{
  "milo": {
    "100": {
      "pregunta": "cual es el main de Milo?",
      "respuesta": "Teemo"
    },
    "200": {
      "pregunta": "cual es el rango de Milo?",
      "respuesta": "madera"
    }
  },
  "poke": {
    "100": {
      "pregunta": "cual es el main de poke?",
      "respuesta": "Teemo"
    },
    "200": {
      "pregunta": "cual es el rango de poke?",
      "respuesta": "madera"
    }
  },
  "pedro": {
    "100": {
      "pregunta": "cual es el main de poke?",
      "respuesta": "Teemo"
    },
    "200": {
      "pregunta": "cual es el rango de poke?",
      "respuesta": "madera"
    }
  },
  "obama": {
    "100": {
      "pregunta": "cual es el main de poke?",
      "respuesta": "Teemo"
    },
    "200": {
      "pregunta": "cual es el rango de poke?",
      "respuesta": "madera"
    }
  },
  "deivi": {
    "100": {
      "pregunta": "cual es el main de poke?",
      "respuesta": "Teemo"
    },
    "200": {
      "pregunta": "cual es el rango de poke?",
      "respuesta": "madera"
    }
  },
  "urrego": {
    "100": {
      "pregunta": "cual es el main de poke?",
      "respuesta": "Teemo"
    },
    "200": {
      "pregunta": "cual es el rango de poke?",
      "respuesta": "madera"
    }
  }
  

  
}
